Survive the search. Survive each other.
Against the Ice is a drama, adventure, history film directed by Peter Flinth.
In 1909, two explorers fight to survive after they're left behind
while on a Danish expedition in ice-covered Greenland.
Captain Ejnar Mikkelsen, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Iver Iversen, played by Joe Cole.
Minister Neergaard, played by Charles Dance.
Naja Holm, played by Heida Reed.
Jørgensen, played by Gísli Örn Garðarsson.
Laub, played by Sam Redford.
Against the Ice is a 2022 historical survival film directed by Peter Flinth and written by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau
and Joe Derrick, based on the true story recounted in Two Against the Ice by Ejnar Mikkelsen.
It stars Coster-Waldau, Joe Cole, Charles Dance, and Heida Reed.
The film was shot in Iceland and Greenland.
Against the Ice premiered at the 72nd Berlin
International Film Festival on February 15, 2022.
It was released on Netflix on March 2, 2022, and
received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, based on true
story, survival, struggle for survival, greenland.
The tone is emotional.